var questions = [
  {
    question: "JavaScript does which of the following?",
    choice1: "1. It defines the content of the web pages",
    choice2: "2. It specifies the layout of the web pages",
    choice3: "3. It programs the behavior of the web pages",
    choice4: "4. It hosts the webpage",
    rightAnswer: "3. It programs the behavior of the web pages"
    },
  {
    question: "JavaScript can select an element by using which method?",
    choice1: "1. getElementById",
    choice2: "2. getElementsByClassName",
    choice3: "3. getElementsByTagName",
    choice4: "4. All of the above",
    rightAnswer: "4. All of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "Create an alert box by using this method",
    choice1: "1. window.alert()",
    choice2: "2. console.log()",
    choice3: "3. document.write()",
    choice4: "4. innerHTML",
    rightAnswer: "1. window.alert()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following NOT is a common data type?",
    choice1: "1. holder",
    choice2: "2. variable",
    choice3: "3. number",
    choice4: "4. object",
    rightAnswer: "1. holder"
  },
  {
    question: "5.	What is the keyword to declare a variable?",
    choice1: "1. set",
    choice2: "2. var",
    choice3: "3. know",
    choice4: "4. as",
    rightAnswer: "2. var"
  },
  {
    question: "What are strings enclosed in?",
    choice1: "1. dollar signs",
    choice2: "2. quotation marks",
    choice3: "3. brackets",
    choice4: "4. parentheses",
    rightAnswer: "2. quotation marks"
  },
  {
    question: "What keyword declares a function?",
    choice1: "1. function",
    choice2: "2. var",
    choice3: "3. let",
    choice4: "4. when",
    rightAnswer: "1. function"
  },
  {
    question: "Objects can have:",
    choice1: "1. properties",
    choice2: "2. methods",
    choice3: "3. values",
    choice4: "4. all of the above",
    rightAnswer: "4. all of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "Arrays are enclosed in:",
    choice1: "1. quotation marks",
    choice2: "2. asterisks",
    choice3: "3. square brackets",
    choice4: "4. parentheses",
    rightAnswer: "3. square brackets"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not an event?",
    choice1: "1. onclick",
    choice2: "2. onmouseover",
    choice3: "3. onmouseout",
    choice4: "4. onexit",
    rightAnswer: "4. onexit"
  }
]
